>> Brian Holt: 好，这是一个箭头函数，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
this is an arrow function, right?
我们要放进去的是
And what we're gonna
put inside of here is,
我们要回去了
we're going to put return,
>> Brian Holt: React.createElement， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: React.createElement,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
然后你不一定能看到这个自动完成的
And then you may not necessarily
see this auto-complete,
如果 VS 码能赶上你要做的事
it'll take a second for VS Code to just
catch up with what you are doing, but
你就可以不理会了
you can just ignore that for now.
迪夫 - 迪夫好吧
Div div, okay.
空的物体然后我们再放
Empty object and
then here we are gonna put again,
reet.createElement，然后我们将放入 h1，
react.createElement, then we're
gonna put inside of that an h1,
>> Brian Holt: 使用空对象和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: With an empty object and
通过我， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
Adopt Me,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
>> Brian Holt: 我们在这里做的是创建一个名为 App的组件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what we've done here
is we've created a component called App.
而这个特定案例中的一个组件只是一个功能
And a component in this particular case
is just a function that whenever it
返回 reet.createElement 的结果。
returns a result of react.createElement.
让我们聊一聊 createElement 是什么，
So let's chat for
a second about what createElement is,
或者哪个应用程序是第二个
or what app is for a second rather.
我喜欢把这个形容为橡皮图章，对吧 ?
I like to describe this as a rubber stamp,
right?
所以我们在这里制作了一个叫做应用的橡皮图章，对吧 ?
So here we have created our own
rubber stamp called app, right?
现在你可以去店里买个橡皮图章
Now, you can go to the store and
you can buy a rubber stamp, but
自己的邮票本身并不有用，对吧 ?
a stamp by itself is not in and
of itself useful, right?
只是想戳它才有用，对吧 ?
It's only useful when you
actually want to stamp it, right?
所以我们创建了一个，我们还没有使用这个邮票，
So here we've created one,
we haven't actually used the stamp,
我们刚创建了邮票
we've just created the stamp.
这就是这个功能的作用
So that's what this function does,
它能让你像你想要的一样多地去印吗
is it allows you to basically stamp
this as many times as you want, okay?
React.createElement 在此处，
React.createElement in here,
这其实是在戳什么东西对吧
what this is actually doing is it's
stamping something here, right?
所以当应用程序被调用时，它就会戳到一个 div ，
So anytime that app gets called,
it's going to stamp a div, and
它将会在一小时内盖章
inside of that it's going to stamp an h1.
> > Brian Holt: 实际上，所有组件都在 React中，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
that's really all components are in React,
就是只回报标记的东西对吧
is it's just something that
returns markup basically, right?
所以，我们又创造了应用，但它本身并没有做任何事情，对吗 ?
So again, we've created app, but this in
it of itself doesn't do anything, right?
这就是邮票的创作，所以我们需要去创造它。
This is the creation of the stamp,
so we actually need to go create it.
这样我们就可以通过 ReactDOM.render 来呈现给 DOM 。
So we're going to go render this to
the DOM by saying ReactDOM.render.
React.createElement App ，然后我们将告诉它如何呈现。
React.createElement App and then we're
gonna tell it where to render it.
我们会说 document.getElementById root。
And we're gonna say
document.getElementById root.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这实际上是由于我们的应用
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is actually
going to stamp our App because of
此 React.createElement。
this React.createElement.
因此 React.createElement 可以使用您创建的任何一个戳记，或者
So the React.createElement can take
an either stamp that you've created, or
它可以用一个像这样一个字符串
it can take in a string like this
where it's actually going to literally
做一个 h1，对吧 ?
make an h1, right?
而这将是我们所创造的
Whereas this is going to be
something that we've created,
这将会是一个我们将要输出到 DOM的 h1 。
this is going to be literally an h1
that we're going to output to the DOM.
>> Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And as you may guess,
就会变成根在这里的根
it's going into root which is
going to be this root up here.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，您可以构建最简单的 React 应用程序。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is about
the simplest React App you can build.
所以如果我保存这个， >> Brian Holt:
So if I save this,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And go back
在我的浏览器中，你可以看到你得到了一个漂亮的 " 采用我 " 的标志。
over to my browser here, you can see here
that you get a nice little Adopt Me logo.
>> Brian Holt: 所以说现在用 CSS 来代替它，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So just say now
replaced that with CSS, right?
所以这就是 h1 去的地方，这其实是我们在那里放的 h1 。
So that's where the h1 went, this is
actually the h1 that we put up there.
> > Brian Holt: 现在我们完成工作坊，你可以回家了，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now we're done with
the workshop and you can go home,
我开玩笑的
I'm just kidding.
我要再用五次这个玩笑别担心
I'm gonna use that joke five more times,
so don't even worry about it.
> > Brian Holt: 因此，这就是 React 的力量，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So,
this is the power of React is one,
这在我看来不是很复杂。
this is not very
complicated in my opinion.
你可以做这个判断，但最简单的是，这就是 React 的内容。
You can be the judge to that, but
at its simplest, this is what React is.
它是用一个组件，就用它，对吧 ?
It's taking a component and
just using it, right?
而这里的力量是我可以制造组件内部的组件
And the power here is that I can make
components that I put inside of components
我放进了组件里面的组件对吧
that I put inside of components that
I put inside of components, right?
所以你有了这个 " 雷法" 的合成模型
So you kinda have this
composability model with React.